Alright jump and justify expert, here we go.
Well, welcome to the show, so good to have you here.
Welcome to Music to My Ears.
I'm your host Janice Willby, and please, let us know who you are.
My name is Carl Fudrickson, and I am a world class expert in the flute.
Carl is an expert in all things flute related.
Tell me, how did you get interested in flutes.
When I was a little boy my oldest sister took flute lessons and I loved the sound of her playing them, so I became fascinated with this great instrument.
Well that's nice, a little family story there.
So, tell me about the ocean.
Well the ocean is the greatest flute player in the history of the world.
The waters rush into the top, interact with the air, much like a human lips do on the flute mouthpiece, and this was an inspiration for the first flute players were listening to the ocean at the seaside.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yes.
And, the stock market crash?
Was caused by flute playing, yes.
Like the pipe piper.
In October of nineteen twenty-nine, a young boy whose father was a stockbroker who never paid any attention to him stood outside the Wall Street stock exchange and played the flute, and all of the stockbrokers left out like the rats, and no one was there to trade the stock, and it caused the great depression.
That is fascinating.
I had no idea.
Now, one more question.
Sure.
I have heard something about my left sock.
Ha ha.
Your left sock is actually is a mouthpiece of your leg flute, that is been surgically implanted in anticipation of today's show, so if you would hold your ankle up to my mouth I will play your leg like a flute, see.
Wow, well we'll have to do that when we come back from break.
Yes.
What a wonderful.
I just didn't know any of that stuff about flutes, and I thank you for being here today.
Your very welcome.
OK, scene.
So that's a little bit of that jump and justify expert game, where we're setting up leaps in logic or information and then connecting these ideas that seem first to be disconnected.
And we also learned about the leg flute.
The leg flute.
So that is jump and justify expert.